createforless.com 2016-04-08

# Privacy Policy -- CreateForLess

It is CreateForLess' policy to respect and protect the privacy of our customers and the users of the CreateForLess site. We understand and share your concern about privacy. Through this Internet Privacy Statement, we want to reassure users of the Site that we will not sell, share, or rent user information to others in a manner different than as set forth in this Internet Privacy Statement.

**Security Information and Secure Ordering**  
Strong precautions are taken to protect the information of the users of our Site. When users submit sensitive information via the Site, that Information is protected both online and off-line.

We take credit card information security seriously and use a variety of technical solutions to make shopping safe at our Site. Furthermore, your information and is protected utilizing the industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption software. The information you send us is encrypted on your computer, sent through the Internet as jumbled code, and decoded at CreateForLess' secure site. While on a secure page, such as our Order Detail page, the lock icon appears on the bottom of your Web browser, such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer. The lock appears closed, as opposed to un-locked, or open, as it is shown when you are just 'surfing'.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also protect user information off-line. All of the information of our Site's users, including the sensitive information for ordering, is maintained in a restricted area. CreateForLess employs the latest security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. Servers are housed in a secure location behind firewalls, and we restrict the number of CreateForLess employees who can access personal data. Furthermore, our employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices

**Placing Orders and Information Collection**  
CreateForLess will not collect or retain any information about you personally (such as, your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) unless you provide it to us voluntarily. We will collect information from the CreateForLess Website in several ways. If you register for an online account, we will ask you for personal information including your name, zip code, e-mail address and phone number. This personal information will be stored in your personal profile. Once you have submitted this information and chosen both a valid username and password, you will be able to take full advantage of using the CreateForLess Website. When you make a purchase from the CreateForLess Website, we will also ask for your credit card information, as well as, billing and shipping information. We will send out confirming e-mails whenever you make a purchase, to inform you that we received your personal information or to confirm your purchase.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
CreateForLess will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:

  * We have your consent to share the information;
  * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;
  * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of CreateForLess to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
  * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the CreateForLess Terms and Conditions, or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

If you do provide us with personal information, we may retain information about your previous purchases of CreateForLess products in order to customize our Website services for your future visits to the site. Second, we may use your e-mail address to send you updates about new products, specials and other items of interest. If you have already submitted this information and would like to remove it, you can delete this information from your personal profile. However, if you made a purchase, we will need to retain certain information for billing and shipping purposes.

**Opting out**  
Any personal information that you provide to CreateForLess may be used for marketing or promotional purposes by CreateForLess. The information provided may also be used for the following: to communicate new products, specials and other items of interest from CreateForLess, communicate offers from other companies that offer products or services of value to you. If you object to these uses for any reason, or no reason at all, you may opt to remove your personal information from our database by unsubscribing to any e-mail you may receive from CreateForLess, or by sending an e-mail request to [info@CreateForLess.com](mailto:info@CreateForLess.com).

**Links to External and Co-Branded Websites**  
We cannot ensure the protection of any personal information that you provide to a third-party site that links to or from the CreateForLess Website, since these third-party sites are owned and operated independently. These third-party sites may have their separate privacy and data collection practices that are beyond our control. Any personal information that you provide to these third-party sites will be regulated by their privacy policy, if any. CreateForLess can assume no responsibility or liability whatsoever for the practices, actions or policies of these third-party sites, and cannot be responsible for the content or privacy practices of such sites.

**Consent**  
By using this Website, you agree to this Security and Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the CreateForLess Website. CreateForLess reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Your continued use of the CreateForLess Website following the posting of changes to our Privacy Policy will signify your acceptance of those changes

**Surveys & Contests**  
From time-to-time we may request information from the users of the Site via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary, and the users of the Site have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as your name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level, etc.). We use such information to notify contest winners, award prizes, and for analyzing the Site traffic to improve the user's experience on the Site.

**Cookies**  
You may have heard of the term "cookies". Cookies are routinely used by most, if not all, E- commerce merchants, including CreateForLess. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's hard drive through the Web browser program containing information about the user which enables us to track and personalize the Site to enhance your experience. For instance, by setting a cookie on our Site, we can provide you with storage of items in your shopping cart between visits. However, if a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our Site although we will be unable to provide our users with the personalized shopping experience we can offer using the cookie data. CreateForLess does not use cookies, or other nonconsensual methods, to take personally identifiable or online contact information about specific users. If you have any questions about our use of cookies, please contact us at [info@CreateForLess.com](mailto:info@CreateForLess.com).

**Google Advertising  
** In order to ensure this website is advertised to the right people, CreateForLess uses Google Advertising Services to only reach out to those that would be interested in our site. This includes location information, interests, and other identifiers. CreateForLess does not acquire any contact information or indentifying information.

This website uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to our site. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven’t completed a task on our site, for example placing items in a shopping cart without purchasing. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the CreateForLess website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy.

**Special Offers, Account Updates and Opting Out**  
CreateForLess occasionally sends our customers and the users of the Site announcements and updates, which contain important information about the Site and service offerings which we believe to be of value to our customers and users. In order to do this, we may enhance or merge the information we collect on the Site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to our customers and users.

We may communicate with the users of the Site via e-mail, telephone, mail, or fax in order to provide requested services, content, product information, notification of special offers, or in regard to customer service issues relating to an account. The users of the Site are always given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their online information used for purposes not directly related to the Site. This option is available when we ask for the information or when the user receives an online requested promotional communication.

For example, our e-mail messages have an "unsubscribe" feature for users of the Site who buy from us, but don't want to be notified about special offers in the future. Users can simply "Reply" back to the e-mail message and type "unsubscribe" in the subject field. Upon receipt of the reply, CreateForLess will remove that e-mail address from our e-mail list. If a user has more than one e- mail address, he or she should include the other addresses as well to ensure proper updating of their account information.

Users of the Site can always update the personally identifying information that they have provided to CreateForLess simply by accessing and updating their account information on the Site or by e-mailing us at [info@createforless.com](mailto:info@createforless.com).

At CreateForLess, your privacy and security are very important to us. If you have any questions about our policies, the practices of our site, or your dealings with CreateForLess, please e-mail us at [info@createforless.com](mailto:info@createforless.com).
